

# Gustavo Yunier Leyte-Vidal Chacón

SOFTWARE ENGINEER • FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT

✓ glcdmx@gmail.com

+5356274921

Y Havana, Cuba

MY LINKS

gustavoylc

y gustavoylc

in gustavoylc

mnf.red/gustavoylc

## Languages

Spanish



English



### Introduction

I am a Frontend Developer with more than 9 years of experience in the field. I have a passion for web development. I'm always up for a challenge and eager to learn more. I would love to collaborate in a high-impact project to enhance my professional knowledge.

# My skills



Adaptability to change



Continuous learning



Ability to receive feedback

# **Technologies and tools**

#### **I MASTER**

CSS / HTML / Figma / Tailwind / TypeScript / MaterialUI / Sass / Postman / React / NextJS / Git / JavaScript / Jest

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE/CAREER



### Frontend Developer

Feb 2023 — TODAY (2 months)

Front10 is an innovative company focused on frontend development and digital product engineering. My experience with Next.js allows me to collaborate on challenging projects and contribute to the growth and success of our client portfolio.

#### **TECHNOLOGIES AND TOOLS**

JavaScript / React / NextJS



# Office of the Historian of Havana

Fullstack Developer at Documentary Heritage

Dec 2013 — Sep 2021 (7 yrs. and 10 months)

A developer, who is a member of a team that includes librarians, curators, archivists, and even a photo library, strives to address existing issues by employing technology and adhering to best programming practices, as this approach would empower executives to make crucial decisions.

#### **TECHNOLOGIES AND TOOLS**

JavaScript / HTML / CSS

# EDUCATION/**DEGREES**

## **Degrees**



UCI

University of Informatic Sciences
 Sep 2007 — Jul 2012 (4 yrs. and 11 months)

#### **Certificates**



### EF SET English Certificate 46/100 (B1 Intermediate)

Issued by: EF Standard English Test (EF SET)

Jan 2023 — TODAY (3 months)



### Platzi learning platform

Issued by: Platzi

Mar 2021 — TODAY (2 yrs. and 1 month)



# **BUT WAIT...** THERE'S EVEN MORE IN MY PROFILE.

This is a short version of my Profile, but a longer one is available where you can see more interesting and relevant data.

+ Click here or scan the QR code